

## ABOUT ME

A software engineer with hands-on experience in a variety of development and engineering positions. Willing to take ownership of core components.

Believer in self-training, especially in the modern world, where constant learning is the best way for geeks to stay synchronized with rapidly evolving technology.

## Skills

Highly involved on understanding business requirements and translating it into specific software design subsequently create a development solution mostly java-based services using latest technologies.

Ability to work as individual or within a team to deliver results.

Has very good experience on E-commerce, E-payment, accounting and promotions businesses.

Excellent experience in restful web services API to expose functionality for 3rd party integration

Excellent experience in reporting using jasper reports engine.

Very Basic in front-end development React/AngularJs/Bootstrap.

# Rabi' Ibrahim

Phone: +(962) 7970498292 Email: ribra92@icloud.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/rabiibrahim

# Experience

Amazon.com

SDE II (2017 - Now)

Working within a high-tech team around the globe to launch amazon.AE, support MENA payment experience, migrate Souq.com data and support amazon distributed services.

#### Payfort.com

Software Engineer-Java (2016 - 2017)

Working on an awesome start-up payment gateway. Build a restful APIs service to support business needs to provide a trusted e-payment solution allows customers to pay online!

#### BluLogix.com

Software Engineer-Java (2014 - 2016)

Working on a cloud billing platform for telecom operators. Build a Restful APIs service that's designed to enable service providers to capture new revenue opportunities and further improve customer service.

### Education

Hashemite University (2011 - 2014)Software Engineering with (GPA 3.13 out of 4).